<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ShopifyTask</string>
    <string name="info_message_total_cost">Total Cost:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_me">Devesh Shetty</string>


    <string name="content_devesh_shetty">
    "I\'m a Computer Engineering student at Xavier Institute of Engineering, Mumbai, India.\n\n"

  "What do I do?\n\n"

        "I code, recode, decode.\n"

        "I watch Anime.\n"

        "\t\t\t....Loading....\n\n\n"

        "The list is HUGE!\n"

        "I like to code in JAVA. I\'m currently exploring lambda expressions.\n\n"

        "I like to try out new things.\n"

        "I have developed Android Applications, Websites and soon will get into iOS Application Development."

        "I am currently working on developing an Augmented Reality based Tetris game.\n\n"

        "Augmented Reality is totally a new field for me.\n\n"

        "My idea for Hack Days revolves around <b>Augmented Reality</b>. \n\n"

        "Let\'s say, we are somehow able to encode the cart item data into a image pattern. My application will recognise that pattern and generate a 3d image of the item. In the prototype, I am making use of the pre-defined hiro pattern and generating a Cube
        with all it\'s properties defined in it\'s class. I have used the ARToolkit framework for the prototype.\n\n"
        "So, customers with the help of our companion application will be able to view the product in it\'s
        fully glory (as a virtual object) and it will be a totally magical experience for them. They can interact
        with the product in a way that\'s unique on its own. We can provide our customers with the facility to customise the product (like color,etc)
        in real-time.\n\n"

        <i>"With this technology, we won\'t just be redefining commerce, we will be bringing an experience to our customers that\'s going
            to blow their minds.\n\n\n"</i>

        </string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
